Guide to the Consumer Reports. Colston E. Warne papers, 1910-1995 and undated RL.11784
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Organizations, 1924-1981 and undated; 2
  - International, 1939-1981; 2
    - Czechoslovakia, 1967-1970 (Box 39)
    - Denmark, 1959-1967 (Box 39)
    - Egypt, 1977 (Box 39)
    - England, 1939-1960; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - England, 1961-1979; 3 folders (Box 40)
    - Fiji, 1971-1974 (Box 40)
    - Finland, 1970-1979 (Box 40)
    - France, 1956-1981 (Box 40)
    - Germany, 1956-1980; 3 folders (Box 40a)
    - Ghana, 1970-1979 (Box 40a)
    - Greece, 1970-1980 (Box 40a)
    - Guyana, 1972-1976 (Box 40a)
    - Hong Kong, 1977-1978 (Box 40a)
    - Hungary, 1968-1970 (Box 40a)
    - Iceland, 1959-1970 (Box 40a)
    - India, 1959-1979; 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Indonesia, 1969-1971 (Box 41)
    - Ireland, 1957-1969 (Box 41)
    - Israel, 1957-1979; 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Italy, 1955-1978 (Box 41)
    - Jamaica, 1962-1978 (Box 41)
    - Japan, 1956-1980; 5 folders (Box 41a)
    - Kenya, 1965-1975 (Box 42)
    - Korea, 1963-1979 (Box 42)
    - Liberia, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Luxembourg, 1968-1972 (Box 42)
    - Malaysia, 1969-1975 (Box 42)
    - Mauritius, 1970 (Box 42)
    - Mexico, 1965-1976 (Box 42)
    - Nepal, 1969-1971 (Box 42)
    - Netherlands, 1960-1975 (Box 42)
    - New South Wales, 1970 (Box 42)
    - New Zealand, 1959-1977 (Box 42)
    - Nigeria, 1966-1977 (Box 42)
    - Norway, 1958-1974 (Box 42)
    - Pakistan, 1962-1974 (Box 42)
    - Panama, 1970 (Box 42)
    - Peru, 1966-1969 (Box 42)
    - Philippines, 1963-1979 (Box 42a)
    - Poland, 1965-1976 (Box 42a)
    - Portugal, 1972-1975 (Box 43)
    - Puerto Rico, 1959-1976 (Box 43)
    - Singapore, 1971-1975 (Box 43)
    - South Africa, 1958-1978 (Box 43)
    - Spain, 1967-1979 (Box 43)
    - Sri Lanka, 1974 (Box 43)
    - Sweden, 1951-1970 (Box 43)
    - Switzerland, 1960-1975; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Thailand, 1967-1978 (Box 43)
    - Trinidad, 1968-1975 (Box 43)
    - USSR, 1964-1978 (Box 43)
    - Venezuela, 1967-1976 (Box 43)
    - Yugoslavia, 1956-1973 (Box 43)
  - State and Local, 1944-1977; 3
    - Alaska, 1964 (Box 44)
    - Arizona, 1966-1974 (Box 44)
    - California, 1959-1974; 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Chicago, 1959-1967 (Box 44)
    - Cincinnati, 1962-1964 (Box 44)
    - Connecticut, 1959-1971 (Box 44)
    - Delaware, 1963-1964 (Box 44)
    - Florida, 1959-1974 (Box 44)
    - Georgia, 1965-1968 (Box 44)
    - Hawaii, 1966-1969 (Box 44)
    - Illinois, 1964-1969 (Box 44)
    - Indiana, 1967-1968 (Box 44)
    - Iowa, 1970-1973 (Box 44)
    - Kansas, 1962-1966 (Box 44)
    - Maryland, 1962-1967 (Box 44)
    - Massachusetts, 1952-1977; 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Michigan, 1958-1971 (Box 45)
    - Minnesota, 1955-1969 (Box 45)
    - Missouri, 1964-1966 (Box 45)
    - Nevada, 1972 (Box 45)
    - New Jersey, 1963-1964 (Box 45)
    - New Mexico, 1964-1965 (Box 45)
    - New York City, 1954-1970 (Box 45)
    - New York State, 1944-1976 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina, 1968 (Box 45)
    - Ohio, 1964-1974 (Box 45)
    - Oklahoma, 1973 (Box 45)
    - Oregon, 1968-1969 (Box 45)
    - Pennsylvania, 1959-1970 (Box 45)
    - Rhode Island, 1966-1968 (Box 45)
    - Texas, 1965-1966 (Box 45)
    - Utah, 1968 (Box 45)
    - Vermont, 1964-1970 (Box 45)
    - Virginia, 1965-1973 (Box 45)
    - Washington, 1961-1969 (Box 45)
    - Wisconsin, 1963-1967 (Box 45)
- Government, 1933-1979 and undated; 3
  - National Recovery Administration Consumer Advisory Board, 1933-1935; 3 folders (Box 46)
  - National Emergency Council Consumer Division, 1934 (Box 46)
  - National Defense Advisory Commission Consumer Division, 1940-1941; 3 folders (Box 46)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Committee, 1944-1946; 3 folders (Box 46)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Committee, 1947-1958; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Executive and District Committees, 1944-1946 (Box 47)
  - Council of Economic Advisors--Consumers Union report "The Government Regulatory Agencies", 1955 (Box 47)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council, 1961-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Angevine, David, 1962-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Campbell, Persia, 1962-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Canoyer, Helen, 1962-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Du Brul, Stephen, 1962-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Heller, Walter, 1962-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Holton, Richard, 1963 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Lampman, Robert, 1962-1963 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Lee, Percy Maxim, 1963-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Low, Florence, 1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Mondale, Walter, 1963 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Morse, Richard L.D., 1962-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Nelson, Helen, 1962-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Peterson, Esther, 1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Porter, Sylvia, 1962 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Ware, Caroline, 1963-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Willis, Betty, 1962-1964 (Box 48)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 49)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Minutes, 1962-1964; 3 folders (Box 49)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Committee on Standards, Grades and Labels, 1962-1964 and undated; 4 folders (Box 49)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Committees, 1963-1964 (Box 49)
  - Council of Economic Advisors Consumer Advisory Council--Various government agencies, 1962-1964; 2 folders (Box 50)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes: Agriculture Department, Civil Aeronautics Board, Commerce Department, Defense Department, Federal Aviation Board, Federal Trade Commission, Food and Drug Administration, General Services Administration, Government Printing Office, Housing and Home Finance Agency, Interior Department, Interstate Commerce Commission, Labor Department, Post Office, Treasury Department, United States Information Agency, Veterans Administration
  - President's Committee on Consumer Interests, 1963-1970; 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1933-1974 (Box 51)
  - Department of Commerce, 1933-1977 (Box 51)
  - Department of Commerce--Ad hoc Committee on Standardization, 1963 (Box 51)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1938-1979; 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare--Committee on Nutrition, 1969 (Box 51)
  - Department of Interior, 1938-1944 (Box 51)
  - Department of Justice, 1943-1966 (Box 51)
  - Department of Labor, 1936-1967 (Box 51)
  - Department of State, 1947-1967 (Box 51)
  - Department of Treasury, 1941 (Box 51)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1945 (Box 51)
  - Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1976 (Box 51)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1943-1972 (Box 51)
  - Federal Power Commission Executive Advisory Committee for the National Power Survey, 1972-1973 (Box 51)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1972 (Box 52)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1971 (Box 52)
  - War Manpower Commission, 1942 (Box 52)
  - Office of Civilian Defense, 1942 (Box 52)
  - Office of Civilian Supply, 1942-1943 (Box 52)
  - Office of Price Administration regional offices (Boston, Springfield), 1942-1947 (Box 52)
  - Office of War Information, 1942 (Box 52)
  - Cost of Living Council Economic Stabilization Program, 1973 (Box 52)
  - General Services Administration, 1971-1975 (Box 52)
  - Kennedy Consumer Protection Program, 1962 (Box 52)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1945 (Box 52)
  - Veterans Administration, 1943 (Box 52)
  - War and Shipping Administration, undated (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 52)
  - National Consumer Energy Advisory Committee, 1973; 2 folders (Box 52)
  - National Consumer Energy Advisory Committee, 1974-1975; 5 folders (Box 52)
  - National Citizens Coalition for the Windfall Profits Tax, 1979 (Box 53)
- Subjects, 1920-1979 and undated; 4
  - Academic Freedom--Jerome Davis, 1936-1937 (Box 53)
  - Academic Freedom--Ralph Gundlach, 1948-1951; 2 folders (Box 53)
  - Academic Freedom--Report on Activities and Associations 1930-1953, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - Bank failure, 1925-1926 (Box 53)
  - Columbia University Graduate School of Business Executive Program in Business Administration, 1959-1961 (Box 53)
  - Conferences, 1939-1958 (Box 53)
  - Conferences, 1958-1969; 6 folders (Box 54)
  - Conferences, 1970-1977; 4 folders (Box 55)
  - Connecticut Valley Branch of the Committee on Unemployment, 1932 (Box 55)
  - Consumer education, 1936-1967 (Box 55)
  - Consumer movement, 1924-1943; 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Cost of living (notes), undated (Box 56)
  - Credit, 1956-1969 (Box 56)
  - Fair trade, 1952 (Box 56)
  - Fisheries, 1943-1944 (Box 56)
  - Food, 1933-1967 (Box 56)
  - Insurance, 1933-1975; 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Labeling, 1943-1972 (Box 56)
  - Labor, 1926-1941 (Box 56)
  - Labor--Opposition to Smith Amendments to the National Labor Relations Act, 1939-1940; 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Labor--Opposition to Smith Amendments to the National Labor Relations Act, 1940 (Box 57)
  - Leisure (notes), undated (Box 57)
  - Loyalty oath issue, 1947-1949; 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Radio, undated (Box 57)
  - Speeches and lecture engagements, 1926-1971; 6 folders (Box 58)
  - Standardization, 1950-1971; 3 folders (Box 59)
  - Trips, 1920-1959; 7 folders (Box 60)
  - Trips, 1960-1969 and undated; 5 folders (Box 61)
  - War-time advertising, 1939-1951; 7 folders (Box 62)
  - War-time advertising, 1937-1944 and undated; 4 folders (Box 63)
  - Worker education, 1928-1939 (Box 63)
  - Writings, 1926-1979; 3 folders (Box 63)
- General Correspondence, undated; 5
  - Abaukinerler - American Farm Bureau, undated (Box 64)
  - American Friends of Spanish Democracy - Ashelman, undated (Box 64)
  - Asher - Arpes, undated (Box 64)
  - Baart - Bass, undated (Box 64)
  - Bassett - Berman, undated (Box 64)
  - Bern - Blanc, undated (Box 64)
  - Blanchard - Bowoff, undated (Box 65)
  - Boyd - Broome, undated (Box 65)
  - Brostoff - Bymers, undated (Box 65)
  - Cadigan - Casseres, undated (Box 65)
  - Castagnola - Chelnov, undated (Box 65)
  - Cherean - Cohen, undated (Box 65)
  - Coil - Corbridge, undated (Box 66)
  - Corby - Crawford, undated (Box 66)
  - Creek - Czap, undated (Box 66)
  - Dadowrian - Delley, undated (Box 66)
  - Dembitz - Dooley, undated (Box 66)
  - Doremus - Dyer, undated (Box 66)
  - Earle - Elmore, undated (Box 67)
  - Elswit - Eyster, undated (Box 67)
  - Fair - Fincke, undated (Box 67)
  - Fine - Flynn, undated (Box 67)
  - Foenander - Furey, undated (Box 67)
  - Gabel - General Electric, undated (Box 67)
  - General Motors - Goodhue, undated (Box 68)
  - Goodman - Greenfield, undated (Box 68)
  - Greer - Gwynne, undated (Box 68)
  - Haas - Hapgood, undated (Box 68)
  - Harader - Harvey, undated (Box 68)
  - Haserodt - Hemenway, undated (Box 68)
  - Hemond - Hollander, undated (Box 68)
  - Hollifield - Howard, undated (Box 69)
  - Howells - Hymes, undated (Box 69)
  - Ihde - Ithaca, undated (Box 69)
  - Jackson - Jones, C.C., undated (Box 69)
  - Jones, Edgar - Justice, undated (Box 69)
  - Kahn - Keith, undated (Box 69)
  - Kelley - Kelly, undated (Box 69)
  - Kelsey - King, Allan, undated (Box 70)
  - King, George - Kirkland, undated (Box 70)
  - Kirkpatrick - Kythe, undated (Box 70)
  - Labor - Leland, undated (Box 70)
  - Lelener - Lipsitz, undated (Box 70)
  - Lipton - Lynd, undated (Box 70)
  - MacAllister - Marske, undated (Box 71)
  - Martin - Macy, undated (Box 71)
  - Maybee - McGraw, undated (Box 71)
  - McKay - Michelson, undated (Box 71)
  - Michener - Mooney, undated (Box 71)
  - Moore - Murphy, Louise, undated (Box 71)
  - Murphy, Richard - Myers, undated (Box 71)
  - Nadestsky - New Masses, undated (Box 72)
  - New Theatre - Nunn, undated (Box 72)
  - Oaks - Oxenfeldt, undated (Box 72)
  - Pace - Patton, undated (Box 72)
  - Paul - Podjar, undated (Box 72)
  - Poe - Putney, undated (Box 72)
  - Q, undated (Box 72)
  - RKO - Reuther, undated (Box 73)
  - Review - Robinson, undated (Box 73)
  - Rochdale - Rothenberg, undated (Box 73)
  - Rothschild - Ryder, undated (Box 73)
  - Sabin - Sargent, Emily, undated (Box 73)
  - Sargent, Hugh - Schnabel, undated (Box 73)
  - Schneider - Segal, Martin, undated (Box 73)
  - Segal, Melvin - Shepherd, undated (Box 74)
  - Sheridan - Smith, Carolyn, undated (Box 74)
  - Smith, David - Spear, undated (Box 74)
  - Speight - Storer, undated (Box 74)
  - Stose - Szuderski, undated (Box 74)
  - Taber - Teller, undated (Box 74)
  - Tempest - Tonne, undated (Box 75)
  - Toomey - Tyson, undated (Box 75)
  - Uhl - Uphaus, undated (Box 75)
  - Uphoff - Ussher, undated (Box 75)
  - V, undated (Box 75)
  - WMCA - Way, undated (Box 75)
  - Weaver - Whiteman, undated (Box 75)
  - Whiteside - Wilner, undated (Box 75)
  - Wilson - Wyman, undated (Box 76)
  - Y - Z, undated (Box 76)
  - General miscellaneous letters, undated (Box 76)
- University of Pittsburgh, 1921-1930; 6
  - General, 1924-1930; 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Printed material, 1927-1930 (Box 77)
  - Grade book, 1921-1922 (Box 77)
- Amherst College, 1930-1971, 1980 and undated; 7
  - General, 1930-1971; 6 folders (Box 78)
  - Associated Massachusetts Colleges, Connecticut Valley Colleges, 1931-1961 (Box 79)
  - Publication requests, 1930-1955; 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Speakers, 1930-1961; 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Student New York City trips, 1931-1960 (Box 79)
  - Student reference letters, 1931-1959; 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Student reference letters, 1960-1971 (Box 80)
  - Student papers, 1936-1941; 6 folders (Box 80)
  - Student papers, 1941-1968 and undated; 6 folders (Box 81)
  - Class material--Economics 21, undated (Box 81)
  - Class material--Economics 26, undated (Box 82)
  - Class material--Economics 41, 42, 66, 79, undated (Box 82)
  - Class material--American Studies, undated (Box 82)
  - Class material--Asian and African Studies, undated (Box 82)
  - Class material--Problems of Inquiry II, undated (Box 82)
  - Class material--General, undated (Box 82)
  - Application for Sherman Pratt Faculty Fellowship, 1935 (Box 82)
  - Honorary Doctorate, 1980 (Oversize-folder 2)
- Consumers Union of the United States, 1935-1981 and undated; 8
  - Board of Directors, 1935-1980; 4
    - General files, 1935-1958; 7 folders (Box 83)
    - General files, 1959-1967; 7 folders (Box 84)
    - General files, 1968-1976; 6 folders (Box 85)
    - Annual reports, 1941-1975 (Box 85)
    - Committee structure and function, Ad Hoc Committee, 1970-1970 (Box 86)
    - Conflict of Interest Committee, 1974-1980 (Box 86)
    - Consumer Interests Foundation Study Committee, 1973 (Box 86)
    - Education and Grants Committee, 1949-1961; 6 folders (Box 86)
    - Education and Grants Committee, 1962-1971; 6 folders (Box 87)
    - Education and Grants Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 88)
    - Executive Committee, 1938-1975; 4 folders (Box 88)
    - Finance Committee, 1949-1968; 3 folders (Box 88)
    - Implementation of Board directives, 1971-1974 (Box 90)
    - Nominations Committee, 1957-1965; 3 folders (Box 89)
    - Nominations Committee, 1955-1970; 7 folders (Box 90)
    - Nominations Committee, 1970-1973; 8 folders (Box 91)
    - Nominations Committee, 1973-1978; 4 folders (Box 92)
    - Pension Plan Committee, 1953-1966; 2 folders (Box 92)
    - Pension Plan Committee, 1957-1977; 4 folders (Box 93)
    - Policy Committee, 1950-1961; 2 folders (Box 93)
    - Policy Committee, 1962-1971 (Box 93a)
  - Subjects, 1936-1981 and undated; 5
    - Advisory Councils--National Advisory Committee, 1940-1952 (Box 94)
    - Advisory Councils--National Educational Advisory Committee, 1953-1980; 3 folders (Box 94)
    - Advisory Councils--Scientific Advisory Committee, 1960-1976 (Box 94)
    - Consumer Education Council on World Trade, 1973-1978 (Box 94)
    - Annual meetings and conferences, 1940 (Box 94)
    - Annual meetings and conferences, 1941-1957; 7 folders (Box 95)
    - Annual meetings and conferences, 1958-1977; 7 folders (Box 96)
    - Board of Directors retreat, 1973 (Box 96)
    - Annual meetings and conferences, 1979 (Box 97)
    - Board of Directors retreat, 1979 (Box 97)
    - Center for the Study of the Consumer Movement, 1973-1981; 5 folders (Box 97)
    - Consumer Reports, 1953-1960; 3 folders (Box 97)
    - Consumers Technical Institute, 1937-1964 (Box 97)
    - Criticisms of CU, 1961-1971 (Box 98)
    - Criticisms of CU--Subversive charges, 1938-1970; 6 folders (Box 98)
    - Criticisms of CU--Subversive charges, undated; 3 folders (Box 99)
    - Criticisms of CU--Leon Hartman, Ex-Camera, 1939-1964 (Box 99)
    - Criticisms of CU--Suppression of CU advertising, 1936-1951 (Box 99)
    - Elections, 1965-1975; 7 folders (Box 100)
    - Elections, 1975-1976; 5 folders (Box 101)
    - Board of Directors listings, 1965-1979 (Box 101)
    - Executive Director--Arthur Kallet dispute, 1955-1957; 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Executive Director--Arthur Kallet dispute, 1957-1958; 7 folders (Box 102)
    - Executive Director--Wray Smith case, 1963-1965 (Box 103)
    - Executive Director--Walker Sandbach, Performance Audit Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 103)
    - Executive Director--Search, 1957-1973; 8 folders (Box 104)
    - Executive Director--Search, 1973; 2 folders (Box 105)
    - Executive Director--Search candidates, 1973; 3 folders (Box 105)
    - Labor relations, 1939-1961 (Box 106)
    - Labor relations--Charles Marlies dispute, 1939 (Box 106)
    - Labor relations--Strike, 1952-1953 (Box 106)
    - Labor relations--Orangeburg, 1971-1980; 2 folders (Box 106)
    - Legal activities, 1939-1974 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--Bose suit, 1970-1975; 2 folders (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--Consumers' Research, 1957 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--Department of the Interior, 1972 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--C. Jackson Grayson, 1972 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--International Commerce Research Center, 1972 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--Kokusai Shogyu, 1972 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--Parliament cigarettes, 1958 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--Sawhill, 1974 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--Seagram's bourbon, 1969 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--Veteran's Administration, 1968-1969 (Box 107)
    - Legal activities--Weinberg Clothing issue, 1956-1957 (Box 107)
    - Media--Radio--CEW broadcast "The Consumer Looks at Advertising", 1941-1942; 6 folders (Box 108)
    - Media--Television, 1957 (Box 108)
    - Speaking tours, 1938-1939 (Box 108)
    - Speaking tours, 1940-1950; 9 folders (Box 109)
    - Speaking tours, 1951-1971; 8 folders (Box 110)
    - Testing--Automobiles, 1947-1970; 3 folders (Box 111)
    - Washington Office, 1939-1966 (Box 111)
    - Washington Office, 1971-1981; 5 folders (Box 112)
  - Miscellaneous Files, 1937-1975; 6
    - Archives, 1965-1978 (Box 113)
    - Bernard Reis Dispute, 1962-1963; 2 folders (Box 113)
    - Community Services Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 113)
    - CU support of "Department of Consumer", 1968-1969 (Box 113)
    - Income tax exemption issues, 1956-1959 (Box 113)
    - Insurance, 1966-1969 (Box 113)
    - Insurance, 1969-1971 (Box 114)
    - Long-range planning, 1970; 2 folders (Box 114)
    - Media and Consumer, 1972-1973 (Box 114)
    - Media and Consumer, 1973-1975; 2 folders (Box 115)
    - Medical Letter controversy, 1957-1959 (Box 115)
    - Multi-national project, 1972-1975 (Box 115)
    - Property, 1957 (Box 115)
    - Questionnaire, 1956-1959 (Box 115)
    - Taping of Board of Directors meetings by outsiders, 1973-1974 (Box 115)
    - Visitors, 1960-1965 (Box 115)
    - Vitamin C controversy, 1971 (Box 115)
    - World's Fair, 1937-1939 (Box 115)
- Writings, Speeches, Testimonies, 1922-1982 and undated; 9
  - Articles, 1924-1971 and undated; 7
    - 1. The Cooperative Chain Stores of the Illinois Miners, 1924 (Box 116)
    - 2. The Consumers' Cooperative Movement in Illinois, 1925 (Box 116)
    - 3. United States Enters Worst Banking Panic of Century, 1929 (Box 116)
    - 4. Free Pennsylvania's Political Prisoners, 1930 (Box 116)
    - 5. Campaign of Labor Hating Brews, 1934 (Box 116)
    - 6. The Great Dreamer, 1934 (Box 116)
    - 7. Nazi Camps, 1934 (Box 116)
    - 8. Social Credit Plan in Alberta, 1935 (Box 116)
    - 9. Social Credit Plan Misses Fundamentals, 1935 (Box 116)
    - 10. Leading Economists Favor Progressive Tax Reform, 1936 (Box 116)
    - 11. No Depression for Leaders of America, Study Shows, 1936 (Box 116)
    - 12. Protecting Consumers' Rights, 1936 (Box 116)
    - 13. Consumers on the March, 1937 (Box 116)
    - 14. Does Distribution Cost Too Much?, 1939 (Box 116)
    - 15. Pseudo-Consumer Organizations and the Schools, 1940 (Box 116)
    - 16. The Challenge of the Consumer Movement, 1940 (Box 116)
    - 17. Proposed Objectives of the American Consumer Movement, 1940 (Box 116)
    - 18. Consumer Education, A National Responsibility, 1941 (Box 116)
    - 19. War Purposes and War Economics, 1942 (Box 116)
    - 20. Guilt Has Quick Ears, 1943 (Box 116)
    - 21. Armistice or Peace in Coal?, 1943 (Box 116)
    - 22. Painless War Financing?, 1943 (Box 116)
    - 23. Mr. Consumer Takes a Beating, 1943 (Box 116)
    - 24. The Chaos of Modern Retailing, 1943 (Box 116)
    - 25. Cherchez La Femme, 1943 (Box 116)
    - 26. Inflation Is Taxation, 1943 (Box 116)
    - 27. Subsidies The Road to Stabilization, 1944 (Box 116)
    - 28. Grade Labels or Trade Labels?, 1944 (Box 116)
    - 29. Coal Dispute Enters Its Second Year, 1944 (Box 116)
    - 30. Pulling the OPA's Teeth, 1944 (Box 116)
    - 31. What Can We Do With War Plants?, 1944 (Box 116)
    - 32. The Scandal of War-Time Advertising, 1944 (Box 116)
    - 33. The Corporation and the Historian, 1944 (Box 116)
    - 34. A Program for the Department of Commerce, 1945 (Box 116)
    - 35. Is It Too Late to Stop Inflation?, 1945 (Box 116)
    - 36. Consumers Face A Crisis, 1945 (Box 116)
    - 37. Fifty-Two Forty or Fight, 1945 (Box 116)
    - 38. Don't Give Up the Ships!, 1946 (Box 116)
    - 39. Radio Advertising- A National Headache, 1946 (Box 116)
    - 40. Should Price Control Be Retained?, 1946 (Box 116)
    - 41. Boom or Bust?, 1946 (Box 116)
    - 42. John L. Lewis, 1947 (Box 116)
    - 43. Prospects of Reciprocal Trade, 1947 (Box 116)
    - 44. Untitled, on red baiting, 1947 (Box 117)
    - 45. Should Patents on Drugs Be Abolished?, 1950 (Box 117)
    - 46. Untitled, introduction on Ben Marsh, 1953 (Box 117)
    - 47. American Agriculture, 1940-1952, 1954 (Box 117)
    - 48. Consumer Organizations--An International Conference?, 1957 (Box 117)
    - 49. Organized Labor and the Consumer, 1959 (Box 117)
    - 50. Consumer Price Trends Under Eisenhower, 1960 (Box 117)
    - 51. The Influence of Moral and Social Responsibility on Economic Behavior, 1961 (Box 117)
    - 52. The Mockery of Modern Advertising, 1961 (Box 117)
    - 53. Caveat Venditor, 1961 (Box 117)
    - 54. A Little Progress, But A Long Way To Go, 1961 (Box 117)
    - 55. Advertising-A Critic's View, 1962 (Box 117)
    - 56. Achievements of Consumers Union in the U.S.A., 1964 (Box 117)
    - 57. Ten Drastic Legal Changes Needed in Food, Drug, and Cosmetics Field, 1966 (Box 117)
    - 58. A Consumer Assessment of the Supermarket Era, 1966 (Box 117)